

Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



ABOUT ME

Graduated in Management Processes, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I have always had the desire to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally, I got in touch with the technology area about 10 years ago and since the end of 2019, I have returned to the technology area. where I've been studying and taking different courses. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I have learned many new things and evolved day by day.

I will continue to improve myself daily as a Front-end Developer and Software Engineer after graduation, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



EXPERIENCE

E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

2019 - 2021

DT3 Sports
Issuance of sales invoice,
On-site inventory management
and on the company's marketplaces,
creating sales ads,
content creation for campaigns,
website development in React.JS,
image optimization and
page loading,
responsible for ERP Bling integration.

Office Assistant

2014 - 2018

Nova Lik Auto Peças Issuance of Sales Invoice Issuance of Payment Reports Input and Output of Products in Stock.

Quality and Service Technician

2010 - 2013

Arcos Dourados LTDA.
Coordinated employees in their respective functions, for better customer service delivery of a 100% qualitative product.



ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Faculdade Única

2021

Estácio de Sá - RJ

2018 - 2020

MBA Software Engineering

TECHNOLOGIST Management processes



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



HTML - 3 Years of Experience

CSS - 3 Years of Experience

Javascript - 3 Years of Experience

Jquery - 3 Years of Experience

Angular Js - 3 Years of Experience

Bootstrap - 2 Years of Experience

Vue Js - 3 Years of Experience

React Js - 3 Years of Experience

Less - 1 Year of Experience

Sass - 1 Year of Experience

Typescript - 2 Years of Experience

Git - 3 Years of Experience

Github - 3 Years of Experience

GitLab - 3 Months of Experience

Node Js - 3 Years of Experience

UI/UX - 2 Years of Experience

Figma - 2 Years of Experience

Photoshop - 2 Years of Experience

NPM - 3 Years of Experience

Yarn - 3 Years of Experience

AWS - 1 month of Experience

Laravel - 1 month of Experience

Markdown - 1 month of Experience

Evernote - 1 month of Experience

PHP - 1 month of Experience



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - Digital Innovation - 2022

Adobe Professional – Adobe Experience Manager Sites Business Practitioner - 2022

Adobe Professional – Adobe Experience Manager Front-End Developer - 2022

Working with Components in React - 2022

Component architecture and front-end complexity management - 2022

Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021

MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS - FaculdadeIV2 - 2021

Initial Vuejs Course - Vuejs Brazil - 2021

Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ – Udemy – 2020

Digital Security Course - FGV - 2020

Business Financial Education Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Strategic Planning Course for Entrepreneurs - SEBRAE - 2020

Financial Management Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Customer Success Course (How to Conquer and Keep Customers)

– SEBRAE –
2020

Digital Marketing Course for Entrepreneurs - SEBRAE - 2020

Financial Strategy for Growth Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Basic Platform Security Course (CBSP) - Shelter Courses, 2018

Submerged Aircraft Escape Training (HUET) – Shelter Courses, 2018

Administrative Assistant Course - 24-hour Courses - 2016



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



Spanish - Basic

French - Basic

Italian - Basic

English - Advanced



ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Excel

Word

Power Point

Teams

Outlook

Sketch

Wordpress

Shopify

ERP Bling

System Configurations

Windows

Computer Domain

Typing

document archiving

internet in general

Google Chrome

Mozilla

Opera